This is a video that shows the working of the model,
which helps in the detection of the gender and age of the persons
in a meeting room. So, I will just run this code and show how
this works. So,
yeah, it's running over Let's
wait for a minute. Okay,
so here the window has been displayed.
And now when I click on this upload image option,
uh, it displays a screen for selecting the image.
So, I'm clicking just this test tree.
So, as you can see, according to the model,
if the number of persons is less than two,
it should detect as, please upload an image with more than two people.
So, when I click on this detect division gender button,
it shows upload an image with more than two people.
So, I will upload an image.
More than two people, so I will upload this,
so here, so when I click on the detect age and gender,
it shows that there are three males with the respective ages,
so I will also do this with another image,
so here, so it's
showing a male of about 45 years old and a female of 25
years old, so thank you.